Guide to the Jerome T. Barrett Collection, 1913-2010 LAC0007
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- The Friends of Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service History Archive, 1919-2010; Record Group 1; 68.5 Linear Feet
  - Office of Technical Services, 1941-2009; Record Group 1 Series 5; 8 Linear Feet
    - OTS Administrative Files, 1971-2009; 1971-1981; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1; 2 Linear Feet
      This subseries contains general administrative files from the FMCS's Office of Technical Services, for which Jerome Barrett served as the first Executive Director. The materials date from 1971-2009, with the bulk dating from the first decade after the Office's creation in 1973. Included are Barrett's pesonal correspondence and travel vouchers, OTS bulletins, student-intern papers, national seminar speeches, and a variety of other administrative files covering policy, performance goals, the senior executive service, and more.
      - Jerome Barrett Correspondence, 1973-1973; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 139, Folder 1)
      - OTS Bulletins [1/2], 1973-1975; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 139, Folder 2)
      - OTS Bulletins [2/2], 1975-1977; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 139, Folder 3)
      - Seminars, 1972-1975; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 139, Folder 4)
      - National Seminar Speeches, 1975; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 139, Folder 5)
      - Student Intern Papers, 1980; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 139, Folder 6)
      - OTS Planning, 1976-181; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 139, Folder 7)
      - Goody Good Bakeries Dispute Case File, 1971-1975; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 139, Folder 8)
      - Jerome Barrett Travel Vouchers [1/3], 1979-1981; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 140, Folder 1)
      - Jerome Barrett Travel Vouchers [2/3], 1977-1978; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 140, Folder 2)
      - Jerome Barrett Travel Vouchers [3/3], 1973-1977; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 140, Folder 3)
      - Senior Executive Service [1/2], 1979-1981; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 140, Folder 4)
      - Senior Executive Service [2/2], 1979-1981; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 140, Folder 5)
      - FMCS Library Book List, 1978; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 140, Folder 6)
      - Pay For Performance, 1979; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 140, Folder 7)
      - Regional Directors [1/2], 1974-1976; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 141, Folder 1)
      - Regional Directors [2/2], 1974-1976; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 141, Folder 2)
      - Performance Goals and Standards, 1981; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 141, Folder 3)
      - John Wells Era, 1989-1993; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 141, Folder 4)
      - Mediator Code Numbers, 1983-1996; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 141, Folder 5)
      - FMCS Forms, undated; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 141, Folder 6)
      - Travel Policy and Procedures, 1978-2001; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 141, Folder 7)
      - Mediator Background and Pay Rate Progression, 1970s; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 142, Folder 1)
      - FMCS General Counsel, 1975-1981; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 142, Folder 2)
      - Publications Policy, 1976-1977; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 142, Folder 3)
      - Mediator Ethics, 1974-1977; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 142, Folder 4)
      - OTS Positions and Organization, 1976-1977; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 142, Folder 5)
      - FMCS 2009 Annual Report, Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 142, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous, 1974-1976; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - Mediation Activities, 1970-2002; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 2; 1.5 Linear Feet
      This subseries is arranged alphabetically by file title.
      This subseries contains material related to the FMCS and Office of Technical Service's mediation programs dating from 1970-2002. Included are materials dealing with labor-management comittees, health care mediation, public sector mediation, environmental mediation and technical assistance.
      - Alaska State Coastal Management Plan, 1980; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 150, Folder 1)
      - Alternative Dispute Resolution, 1977-1980; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 150, Folder 2)
      - Environmental Mediation, 1973-1982; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 150, Folder 3)
      - FMCS Labor-Management Cooperation Program [1/3], 1980-2002; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 150, Folder 4)
      - FMCS Labor-Management Cooperation Program [2/3], 1981-2002; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 150, Folder 5)
      - FMCS Labor-Management Cooperation Program [3/3], 1979-1983; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 150, Folder 6)
      - FMCS National Labor-Management Conferences, 1986-1996; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 150, Folder 7)
      - Health Care Mediation [1/2], 1974-1979; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 150, Folder 8)
      - Health Care Mediation [2/2], 1974-1979; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 150, Folder 9)
      - Labor-Management Committees, 1980-1981; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 151, Folder 1)
      - National Association of Social Workers [1/3], 1980-1981; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 151, Folder 2)
      - National Association of Social Workers [2/3], 1979-1982; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 151, Folder 3)
      - National Association of Social Workers [3/3], 1978-1979; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 151, Folder 4)
      - Public Sector Mediation [1/4], 1971-1981; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 151, Folder 5)
      - Public Sector Mediation [2/4], 1970-1974; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 151, Folder 6)
      - Public Sector Mediaton [3/4], 1975-1979; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 151, Folder 7)
      - Public Sector Mediation [4/4], 1973; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 151, Folder 8)
      - Technical Assistance, 1979-1980; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 152, Folder 1)
      - U.S. National Committee for Man and the Biosphere, 1978-1980; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 152, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous, 1980-1984; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Mediator Recruitment, Selection and Evaluation, 1964-1982; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 3; 1 Linear Feet
      This subseries contains Office of Technical Services material relating to mediator recruitment, selection and evaluation dating from 1964-1982. Included are mediator applications and evaluations, a mediator recruitment and selection manual, and material on the FMCS' mediator-intern program.
      - Mediator Applications, 1978 May; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 148, Folder 1)
      - Mediator Candidate Evaluation [1/3], 1974; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 148, Folder 2)
      - Mediator Candidate Evaluation [2/3], Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 148, Folder 3)
      - Mediator Candidate Evaluation [3/3], 1977-1978; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 148, Folder 4)
      - Mediator Evaluation, 1974-1975; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 148, Folder 5)
      - Mediator-Interns, 1974-1975; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 148, Folder 6)
      - Mediator Interview Material, 1974; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 148, Folder 7)
      - Mediator Recruitment and Selection [1/2], 1973-1974; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 148, Folder 8)
      - Mediator Recruitment and Selection [2/2], 1964-1975; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - Mediator Selection Manual [1/2], 1977; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 149, Folder 2)
      - Mediator Selection Manual [2/2], 1977; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 149, Folder 3)
      - Mediator Selection Review Committee, 1976-1977; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 149, Folder 4)
      - Personnel Staffing Report, 1982 April; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - OTS Publications, 1953-1992; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 4; 0.5 Linear Feet
      This subseries contains publications from the FMCS' Office of Technical Services as well as other labor mediation organizations dating from 1953-1992. Included are OTS-produced reports and brochures, as well as papers and articles on topics such as public sector mediation, labor-management committees and resource dispute mediation.
      - Industrial Relations Research Association Papers, 1953; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 4 (Box 147, Folder 1)
      - "Collective Bargaining and Strike Provisions of National Union Constitutions", 1968; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 4 (Box 147, Folder 2)
      - "The Ethics of Social Intervention: Community Crisis Intervention Programs", 1973; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 4 (Box 147, Folder 3)
      - Material for Inclusion in the 1973 Annual Report, Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 4 (Box 147, Folder 4)
      - 1974 OTS Brochure, Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 4 (Box 147, Folder 5)
      - "Public Sector Labor Relations in Retrospect - The Year 1973", 1974; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 4 (Box 147, Folder 6)
      - Pre-Conference Submissions for National Conference on Public Sector Labor Relations Research, 1975; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 4 (Box 147, Folder 7)
      - "A Review of Labor-Management Committees", 1975; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 4 (Box 147, Folder 8)
      - National and Regional Management Conference (FY 77-78 Goals and Budget), 1976; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 4 (Box 147, Folder 9)
      - FMCS Jurisdiction in State and Local Government Employees Disputes, 1981; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 4 (Box 147, Folder 10)
      - "How and When to Mediate Natural Resource Disputes", 1984; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 4 (Box 147, Folder 11)
      - Targeted Specific Bargaining, 1990; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 4 (Box 147, Folder 12)
      - Grievance Mediation, 1992; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 4 (Box 147, Folder 13)
    - OTS Staff Files, 1941-2005; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5; 2 Linear Feet
      This subseries contains files on numerous OTS staff members, including mediators and support staff. The files include reports, memoranda and correspondence related to the day-to-day activities of the OTS and the FMCS in addition to miscellaneous biographical material. The materials date from 1941-2005.
      - Robert Baker, 1994; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 143, Folder 1)
      - Jerome Barrett, 1974-1981; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 143, Folder 2)
      - Hezekia Brown, 2000s; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 143, Folder 3)
      - George Buckingham, 1976; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 143, Folder 4)
      - James Carroll, 1949; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 143, Folder 5)
      - Bonnie Castrey [1/2], 1962-1980; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 143, Folder 6)
      - Bonnie Castrey [2/2], 1969-1981; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 143, Folder 7)
      - Ronald Collotta, 1970-1998; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 143, Folder 8)
      - Harold Davis, 1975-1981; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 143, Folder 9)
      - Gil Donahue, 1976-1977; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 143, Folder 10)
      - Ken Evans, 1996-1998; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 143, Folder 11)
      - Douglass Hammond, 1989-1998; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 143, Folder 12)
      - Mary Lou Hennessy, 1975; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 143, Folder 13)
      - Eileen Hoffman [1/2], 1980-1981; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 143, Folder 14)
      - Eileen Hoffman [2/2], 1980; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 143, Folder 15)
      - Wayne Horvitz, 1977-1978; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 143, Folder 16)
      - Peter Hurtgen, 2004; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 143, Folder 17)
      - Nate Kazin, 1977-2002; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 144, Folder 1)
      - Ed Koenig, 1986; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 144, Folder 2)
      - George Larney, 1974-1975; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 144, Folder 3)
      - Earl Leonheart, 1961-2000; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 144, Folder 4)
      - Ira Lobel, 1973-1974; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 144, Folder 5)
      - John Martin, 1984; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 144, Folder 6)
      - Kenneth Moffett, 1979; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 144, Folder 7)
      - Michael Nowakowski, 1975-1976; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 144, Folder 8)
      - Tom O'Brien, 1978-1998; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 144, Folder 9)
      - Timothy O'Sullivan, 1978-1986; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 144, Folder 10)
      - John Pinto, 1989-1999; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 144, Folder 11)
      - John Popular [1/2], 1975-1977; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 144, Folder 12)
      - John Popular [2/2], 1973-1975; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 144, Folder 13)
      - James Power [1/3], 1975-1978; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 145, Folder 1)
      - James Power [2/3], 1973-1974; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 145, Folder 2)
      - James Power [3/3], 1974-1980; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 145, Folder 3)
      - Samuel Sackman, 1988; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 145, Folder 4)
      - James Schepker, 1985-2002; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 145, Folder 5)
      - Pearl Smith, 1997-2000; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 145, Folder 6)
      - John Stepp, 1979-1980; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 145, Folder 7)
      - Lucretia Dewey Tanner, 1974-1981; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 145, Folder 8)
      - Jack Toner, 2004-2005; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 145, Folder 9)
      - Bert Walters, 1967-1968; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 145, Folder 10)
      - Richard Williams, 1994; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 145, Folder 11)
      - Paul Yager [1/3], 1953-1989; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 146, Folder 1)
      - Paul Yager [2/3], 1951-1985; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 146, Folder 2)
      - Paul Yager [3/3], 1941-1976; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 146, Folder 3)
      - Harvey Young, 1962-1999; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 5 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Training and Professional Development, 1974-1991; 1974-1981; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 6; 0.5 Linear Feet
      This subseries contains material related to OTS mediator training and professional development dating from 1974-1991. Included are workshop and training material as well as memoranda and reports from the FMCS Office of Professional Development.
      - FMCS Management Workshop, 1978; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 6 (Box 153, Folder 1)
      - Mediation Skills Training [1/2], 1978-1997; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 6 (Box 153, Folder 2)
      - Mediation Skills Training [2/2], 1976-1979; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 6 (Box 153, Folder 3)
      - Mediator Techniques Handbooks, 1980; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 6 (Box 153, Folder 4)
      - Office of Professional Development, 1977-1981; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 6 (Box 153, Folder 5)
      - Professional Development, 1974-1978; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 6 (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1971-1997; 1971-1986; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 7; 0.5 Linear Feet
      This subseries is arranged in its original order.
      This subseries cotains a variety of miscellaneous, unsorted material related to the FMCS and Office of Technical Servie mediation, training and professional development, dating from 1971-1997. Included are memoranda, reports, newsletters, mediator training material, conference material, newspaper clippings and handwritten notes.
      - Miscellaneous [1/5], 1972-1978; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 6 (Box 154, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous [2/5], 1971-1991; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 6 (Box 154, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous [3/5], 1971-1985; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 6 (Box 154, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous [4/5], 1977-1986; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 6 (Box 154, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous [5/5], 1978-1997; Record Group 1 Series 5 Subseries 6 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters, Record Group Series 6
    - Caucus Sumer 2011 Special (Box 155A, Folder 1)
    - Caucus Spring 2011 Issue 23 (Box 155A, Folder 2)
    - Caucus Fall 2010 Issue 22 (Box 155A, Folder 3)
    - Caucus Spring 2010 Issue 21 (Box 155A, Folder 4)
    - Caucus Fall 2009 Issue 20 (Box 155A, Folder 5)
    - Caucus Spring 2009 Issue 19 (Box 155A, Folder 6)
    - Caucus Fall 2008 Issue 18 (Box 155A, Folder 7)
    - Caucus Spring 2008 Issue 17 (Box 155A, Folder 8)
    - Caucus Fall 2007 Issue 16 (Box 155A, Folder 9)
    - Caucus Spring 2007 Issue 15 (Box 155A, Folder 10)
    - Caucus Fall 2006 Issue 14 (Box 155A, Folder 11)
    - Caucus Spring 2006 Issue 14 (Box 155A, Folder 12)
    - Caucus Fall 2005 Issue 13 (Box 155A, Folder 13)
    - Caucus Spring 2005 Issue 11 (Box 155A, Folder 14)
    - Caucus Fall 2004 Issue 10 (Box 155A, Folder 15)
    - Caucus Spring 2003 (Box 155A, Folder 16)
    - Various Caucus Issues 2000-2002 (Box 155A, Folder 17)
      May 2000, Aug 2000, Dec 2000, Mar 2001, Mar 2002, and Sept 2002
    - Caucus Fall 2003 Issue 8 (Box 155A, Folder 18)
    - Caucus Spring 2004 Issue 9 (Box 155A, Folder 19)
    - FMCS Newsletter 1962 (Box 155A, Folder 20)
    - FMCS Newsletter 1963 (Box 155A, Folder 21)
    - FMCS Newsletter 1964 (Box 155A, Folder 22)
    - FMCS Newsletter 1965 (Box 155A, Folder 23)
    - FMCS Newsletter 1966 (Box 155A, Folder 24)
    - FMCS Newsletter 1967 (Box 155A, Folder 25)
    - FMCS Newsletter 1968 (Box 155A, Folder 26)
    - FMCS Newsletter 1969 (Box 155A, Folder 27)
    - FMCS Newsletter 1970 (Box 155A, Folder 28)
    - FMCS Newsletter 1971 (Box 155A, Folder 29)
    - FMCS Newsletter 1972 (Box 155A, Folder 30)
    - FMCS Newsletter 1973 (Box 155A, Folder 31)
    - FMCS Newsletter 1974 (Box 155A, Folder 32)
    - The Mediator Newsletter 1974 (Box 155A, Folder 33)
    - The Mediator Newsletter 1975 (Box 155A, Folder 34)
    - The Mediator Newsletter 1976 (Box 155A, Folder 35)
    - The Mediator Newsletter 1977 (Box 155A, Folder 36)
    - The Mediator Newsletter 1978 (Box 155A, Folder 37)
    - The Mediator Newsletter 1979 (Box 155A, Folder 38)
    - The Mediator Newsletter 1981 (Box 155A, Folder 40)
    - The Mediator Newsletter 1982 (Box 155A, Folder 41)
    - The Mediator Newsletter 1989 (Box 155A, Folder 42)
    - The Mediator Newsletter 1990 (Box 155A, Folder 43)
    - The Mediator Newsletter 1991 (Box 155A, Folder 44)
    - The Mediator Newsletter 1992 (Box 155A, Folder 45)
    - The Mediator Newsletter 1995 (Box 155A, Folder 47)
    - The Mediator Newsletter 1996 (Box 155A, Folder 48)
    - FMC Newspaper 1961 (Box 155A, Folder 49)
  - Training Manuals, Record Group 1 Series 7
    - Mediation Training Guides and Labor Law Publications, 1967-1997 (Box 289)
      This box contains multiple mediation training manuals and a small collection of labor law publications.
    - Training Cassettes, 1975-1976 (Box 296)
      This box contains cassette tape mediation training materials.
  - Cassette Tapes, 1971-2000; Record Group 1 Series 8
    This series contains FMCS cassette tapes, including conference cassettes, oral history cassettes, speeches cassettes, and other FMCS events cassettes.
    - Fifth National Labor Managment Conference Cassette Collection, 1984 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Fifth National Labor Managment Conference Cassette Collection, 1984 (Box 157, Folder 6)
      Set of 16 cassettes.
    - Fifth National Labor Managment Conference Cassette Collection, 1984 (Box 157, Folder 7)
      Set of 8 cassettes.
    - Seventh National Labor-Managment Conference Cassette Collection, 1986 (Box 157, Folder 8)
      Set of 12 cassettes.
    - Seventh National Labor-Managment Conference Cassette Collection, 1986 (Box 157, Folder 9)
    - Fourth National Labor-Managment Conference Cassette Collection, 1983 (Box 157, Folder 1)
      Set of 11 cassettes.
    - Fourth National Labor-Managment Conference Cassette Collection, 1983 (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Fourth National Labor-Managment Conference Cassette Collection, 1983 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - National Labor-Managment Conference Cassette Collection (Box 157, Folder 4)
      Set of 11 cassettes. Unknown date or conference number.
    - Tenth Annual National Labor-Managment Conference Cassette Collection, 2000 (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - Tenth Annual National Labor-Managment Conference Cassette Collection, 2000 (Box 157, Folder 11)
      Set of 18 cassettes.
    - Seventh Annual National Labor-Managment Conference Cassette Collection, 1986 (Box 157, Folder 12)
    - Spidr's 26th Annual International Conference Portland, Oregon Cassette Collection, 1998 (Box 157, Folder 13)
      Set of 10 cassettes.
    - National Labor Management Conference Cassette Tapes, 1997-2000 (Box 285)
      This box contains cassette tapes of the 7th and 10th National Labor Management Conferences.
    - Ken Moffett Oral History 1, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 1)
    - Ken Moffett Oral History 2, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 2)
    - Ken Moffett Oral History 3, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 3)
    - Ken Moffett Oral History 4, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 4)
    - Ken Moffett Oral History 6, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 5)
    - Ken Moffett Oral History 7, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 6)
    - Ken Moffett Oral History 8, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 7)
    - Ken Moffett Oral History 9, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 8)
    - J. Curtis Counts Oral History 1, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 9)
    - J. Curtis Counts Oral History 2, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 10)
    - J. Curtis Counts Oral History 3, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 11)
    - J. Curtis Counts Oral History 4, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 12)
    - J. Curtis Counts Oral History 5, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 13)
    - J. Curtis Counts Oral History 6, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 14)
    - J. Curtis Counts Oral History 7, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 15)
    - John Steelman Oral History 1, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 16)
    - John Steelman Oral History 2, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 17)
    - David Cole Oral History 1, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 18)
    - David Cole Oral History 2, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 19)
    - David Cole Oral History 3, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 20)
    - David Cole Oral History 4, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 21)
    - James Dinnery Oral History 1, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 22)
    - James Dinnery Oral History 2, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 23)
    - Bill Simkin Oral History 1, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 24)
    - Bill Simkin Oral History 2, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 25)
    - Bill Simkin Oral History 3, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 26)
    - Bill Simkin Oral History 4, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 27)
    - Bill Simkin Oral History 5, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 28)
    - Bill Simkin Oral History 6, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 29)
    - Bill Usery Oral History 1, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 30)
    - Bill Usery Oral History 2, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 31)
    - Bill Usery Oral History 3, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 32)
    - Bill Usery Oral History 4, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 33)
    - Bill Usery Oral History 5, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 34)
    - Mrs. Cyrus Ching Oral History, Undated (Box 316, Cassette 35)